There are no more patriots, just rebels and tyrants.
xXx: Return of Xander Cage is a action, adventure,
crime film directed by D.J. Caruso.
Xander Cage is left for dead after an incident, though he secretly returns to
action for a new, tough assignment with his handler Augustus Gibbons.
Xander Cage, played by Vin Diesel.
Xiang, played by Donnie Yen.
Adele Wolff, played by Ruby Rose.
Serena Unger, played by Deepika Padukone.
Jane Marke, played by Toni Collette.
Agent Augustus Gibbons, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
XXX: Return of Xander Cage (released as XXX: Reactivated in some
countries) is a 2017 American action spy film directed by D.J.
Caruso and written by F.
Scott Frazier.
The third installment in the XXX film series and a sequel to both XXX (2002) and XXX: State of the Union (2005), it stars Vin Diesel in the title role along
with Donnie Yen, Deepika Padukone, Kris Wu, Ruby Rose, Tony Jaa, Nina Dobrev, Toni Collette, Ariadna Gutiérrez, Hermione Corfield, and Samuel L.
Released on January 20, 2017, in 2D, RealD 3D and IMAX 3D by Paramount Pictures, the film received mixed reviews from critics but was commercially successful, grossing over
$346 million worldwide against a production budget of $85 million and subsequently becoming both the franchise's and Revolution Studios' highest-grossing film.
The film explores themes of airplane, tattoo, spy, extreme sports, parachute.
The tone is intense.